[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So what we're gonna do next
所以我们接下来要做的是
is #Let's show what our
#让我们看看我们的
predictions look like.
预测怎么样
Now I talked about using GraphLab Canvas as a way to visualize data, but
我们之前说过使用GraphLab Canvas来可视化数据，但是
you can also use other tools out there to visualize; other python tools.
你也可以用其他的Python工具
So just as a simple demonstration of that, I'm going to import one search tool.
为了做一个简单的示范 我将导入一个搜索工具
It's a pretty commonly used one.
很常用的一个
It's called mot plot lib.
它叫做 mot plot lib
And so, and from there I'm gonna
现在呢 我要
input something called pipe plot which allows you to do some plotting in Python.
输入pyplot 它可以让你在Python里绘图
And I'm gonna refer to it as PLT.
我准备把它简记为PLT
So when you're doing the importing Python, if you type import myplotlib.pyplot,
所以当你在Python里导入包的时候 如果你输入import myplotlib.pyplot
is a particular piece of the package, and I write as plt.
它是包里一个特定的部分 在它后面我写了as plt
Now I don't have to write this whole thing matlab_lib.pyplot blah blah blah,
这样我就不用一直写这么长串的matlab_lib.pyplot
I just write plt.
我只要写plt就可以
That's why we use the as command.
这就是as命令的作用
So I'm gonna import it, and one little trick I'm gonna do, just like you did with
我现在要导入它 这里有一个小技巧 就像你对
Canvas to make sure it prints inside the notebook I'm gonna do it here too.
Canvas做的那样 确认它在记事本里输出了 我们在这里也要做类似的事情
So you put this percent, and
所以输入百分号%
you say, matplotlib inline.
然后输入 matplotlib inline
So that just plots it on the notebook itself.
所以它会在记事本上绘图
So let's hit Enter.
让我们按下回车
We've imported it, and now I'm going to actually build
我们已经导入了它 现在我要建立
a map plot lib plot for the results, for the initial results.
一个来表示最初结果的图像
So we're gonna plot plt.plot.
我们需要键入 plt.plot
And there's a function here.
这里有一个功能
And I'm gonna plot my test data in two ways.
我会用两种方法绘制我的测试数据
So it's interesting, can plot two multiple plots on top of each other with MyPlot 11.
这太有趣了 我们可以用MyPLot 11在一张图里画出两种图形
We're just gonna do that together.
我们一起来试试看
So I'm gonna take my test data and in my test data I'm
我用测试数据作为参数 在我们使用的测试数据里
gonna plot on the x-axis the square feet of living space.
我将住房面积大小作为X轴
And in the y-axis for my test data, I'm going to plot the price.
将房屋价格作为Y轴
So, this is kind of similar to the plot we did above, the scatter plot.
这和我们之前做过的图有点像 是个散点图
And I'm gonna refer to each one of these points as test points.
这些点中的每一个点都是测试点
I'm gonna draw them as a dot.
我用“.”表示这些点
So, that's what this little dot here does.
这就是这个“.”在这里的作用
However, I'm also going to plot one more thing.
此外 我还要再画一种图形
So I'm going to plot two things on the same plot.
我将在一张图里画两种图形
Actually, so I'm missing a comma up here.
噢 我上面丢掉一个逗号
So in addition to plotting the test data, let's plot our predictions.
所以我们除了绘制测试数据之外 还要把预测画出来
So again, on the x-axis is going to be the square feet of living space,
同样地 这一次x轴依然表示居住空间的面积大小
but on the y-axis, I'm going to plot something else.
但是y轴 跟之前所表示的有所不同
I'm going to plot what my model predicted for each one of those houses.
它用来表示我的模型对每栋房子预测出的价格
So remember we built this square foot model and
记得之前我们建立的这个平方英尺模型
it has many functions associated with it.
它有好多功能可以选择
If you go down, one of those functions it has is called the predict function.
如果你向下翻的话 会有一个功能叫做预测功能
And the predict function, you can give it a bunch of data's input and
这个预测功能就是 你给它输入一串数据
it's gonna output and estimates our column of data with the predictions for
它可以输出并对我们这一列数据中
each one of these input elements.
每一个元素的预测值作出估算
So, I'm giving you the test data and I'm going to draw it as a dash.
我给它传入测试数据 然后用短横线来作图
Now, before I execute this line,
在我执行这一行命令之前
just take a moment to imagine what this plot is going to look like.
我们花一点时间来想象一下这张图会是什么样
So, the top line says plot living space through the price test data with dots.
上面那一行代码指的是用点号来作出 测试数据中房屋大小和价格的图形
It's going to look very similar to the scatterplot that we drew before.
它很像我们之前画过的那张散点图
And the second line says plot
第二行指的是
the input houses living with the prediction with a dash.
用短横线来作出房屋大小和预测价格的图形
And now remember this was a simple linear regression model with a single variable so
要记得这是只有单个变量的简单线性回归模型
all we have is a single variable and
我们只有一个变量
as we covered in the lectures, we just plotted a single line.
就像我们之前在课程里所讲的 我们只会画出一条直线
And we'll see that execute and here we are.
我们执行这两行来看看结果
So the blue dots here are the test data for the houses,
这里蓝色的点 是测试数据中的房价
while the green line corresponds to the predicted house values.
这里绿色的线对应于我们预测的房价
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community